A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1958-1970 FA400
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1968
  - Peru, 1968/331
    - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/331.D
      - A (Reel 57, Frame 445)
    - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/331.E
      - A-Z (Reel 57, Frame 453)
    - Peru - Declinations, 1968/331.F
      - Q-S (Reel 57, Frame 563)
  - El Salvador, 1968/333
    - D-M (Reel 57, Frame 661)
    - El Salvador - Medical Sciences, 1968/333.A
      - University of Salvador (Medical School) (Reel 57, Frame 675)
    - El Salvador - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/333.D
      - Agriculture (Berrios Mendoza, Antonio) (Reel 57, Frame 679)
  - Dominican Republic, 1968/335
    - Dominican Republic - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/335.D
      - Agriculture (A-D) (Reel 57, Frame 695)
  - Uruguay, 1968/337
    - Verde, Luis S. (Reel 57, Frame 702)
    - Uruguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/337.D
      - University of Montevideo (Veterinary Medicine) (Reel 57, Frame 709)
    - Uruguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/337.E
      - Aragunde, Mario C. (Reel 57, Frame 711)
  - Venezuela, 1968/339
    - C-U (Reel 57, Frame 717)
  - Great Britain, 1968/400
    - C-O (Reel 57, Frame 763)
  - England, 1968/401
    - A-H (Reel 57, Frame 795)
    - I-N (Reel 57, Frame 971)
    - O (Reel 58, Frame 1)
    - P-T (Reel 58, Frame 84)
    - Unilever Limited (Parkinson, M. W.) (Reel 58, Frame 219)
    - University (B-M) (Reel 58, Frame 225)
    - University (N-S) (Reel 58, Frame 363)
    - W-Z (Reel 58, Frame 471)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1968/401.A
      - University College (Hospital Medical School) (Reel 58, Frame 503)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/401.E
      - Standley, John (Reel 58, Frame 505)
  - Ireland, 1968/403
    - O-U (Reel 58, Frame 509)
  - Scotland, 1968/405
    - B-U (Reel 58, Frame 526)
  - Wales, 1968/407
    - A-U (Reel 58, Frame 550)
  - Australia, 1968/410
    - A-W (Reel 58, Frame 567)
  - New Zealand, 1968/418
    - R-S (Reel 58, Frame 834)
  - Fiji, 1968/419
    - M-U (Reel 58, Frame 844)
  - Caribbean Region, 1968/420
    - A-M (Reel 58, Frame 853)
    - Caribbean Region - Medical Sciences, 1968/420.A
      - C-H (Reel 58, Frame 882)
  - Guyana, 1968/423
    - C-R (Reel 58, Frame 967)
    - Guyana - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/423.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 58, Frame 988)
  - Canada, 1968/427
    - A-J (Reel 58, Frame 999)
    - K-W (Reel 59, Frame 1)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1968/427.C
      - University of Toronto (School of Nursing) (Reel 59, Frame 167)
    - Canada - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/427.D
      - A (Reel 59, Frame 172)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/427.E
      - C-S (Reel 59, Frame 236)
  - Barbados, 1968/435
    - Barbados - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/435.E
      - Quintyne, Robert (Reel 59, Frame 257)
  - Jamaica, 1968/437
    - D-S (Reel 59, Frame 260)
    - University of the West Indies (C-S) (Reel 59, Frame 379)
    - Jamaica - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/437.D
      - Agriculture (MacMillan, Andrew) (Reel 59, Frame 638)
  - Trinidad and Tobago, 1968/451
    - I-S (Reel 59, Frame 654)
  - Winward Islands, 1968/455
    - St. Lucia Family Planning Association (Reel 59, Frame 658)
    - Winward Islands - Schistosomiasis, 1968/455.W
      - St. Vincent (Reel 59, Frame 664)
  - Sri Lanka, 1968/462
    - Hensmann, C. Richard (Reel 59, Frame 675)
    - Sri Lanka - Natural Sciences, 1968/462.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 59, Frame 694)
    - Sri Lanka - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/462.E
      - Devasunderarajah, N. (Reel 59, Frame 733)
  - Hong Kong, 1968/463
    - U (Reel 59, Frame 738)
  - India, 1968/464
    - A-B (Reel 59, Frame 766)
    - C (Reel 59, Frame 903)
    - Finance (Reel 59, Frame 946)
    - D-H (Reel 59, Frame 998)
    - Indian Agricultural Research Institute (A-W) (Reel 60, Frame 1)
    - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (B-W) (Reel 60, Frame 240)
    - I (Reel 60, Frame 352)
    - J-M (Reel 60, Frame 412)
    - N-O (Reel 60, Frame 572)
    - P-T (Reel 60, Frame 674)
    - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University (Farm Economics) (Reel 60, Frame 884)
    - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University (J-S) (Reel 60, Frame 1088)
    - U-V (Reel 60, Frame 1102)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1968/464.A
      - F-V (Reel 61, Frame 1)
    - India - Nursing, 1968/464.C
      - A-C (Reel 61, Frame 35)
    - India - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/464.D
      - A-U (Reel 61, Frame 52)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/464.E
      - India (Reel 61, Frame 76)
      - B-S (Reel 61, Frame 123)
  - Pakistan, 1968/465
    - A-W (Reel 61, Frame 210)
    - Pakistan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/465.D
      - Agriculture (K-Q) (Reel 61, Frame 357)
  - Iraq, 1968/470
    - Yousiph, Yacoub el (Reel 61, Frame 399)
  - Malaysia, 1968/473
    - A-U (Reel 61, Frame 405)
    - Malaysia - Medical Sciences, 1968/473.A
      - University of Malaya (Reel 61, Frame 437)
  - Africa, 1968/475
    - A-I (Reel 61, Frame 443)
  - Kenya, 1968/476
    - East African Agriculture and Forestry Research Organization (Reel 61, Frame 506)
    - A-O (Reel 61, Frame 682)
    - S-W (Reel 61, Frame 759)
    - Kenya - Medical Sciences, 1968/476.A
      - University College, Nairobi (Physiology) (Reel 61, Frame 1014)
    - Kenya - Natural Sciences, 1968/476.D
      - A-U (Reel 61, Frame 1017)
    - Kenya - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/476.E
      - A-W (Reel 62, Frame 1)
  - East Africa Region, 1968/477
    - Administration (January-May) (Reel 62, Frame 101)
    - Administration (June-August) (Reel 62, Frame 294)
    - Administration (September-October) (Reel 62, Frame 496)
    - Administration (November-December) (Reel 62, Frame 653)
    - East African Community (Reel 62, Frame 745)
    - A-V (Reel 62, Frame 946)
  - Mauritius, 1968/478
    - Agriculture (Reel 62, Frame 1164)
    - Mauritius - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/478.E
      - Narain, Tiberman Mohunji (Reel 62, Frame 1168)
  - Malawi, 1968/482
    - Malawi - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/482.E
      - Moghogho, Lewis Kajera (Reel 62, Frame 1174)
  - Rhodesia, 1968/483
    - Gelfand, Michael (Reel 62, Frame 1179)
  - South Africa Region, 1968/487
    - South Africa Region - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/487.E
      - Ndlowu, C. P. (Reel 62, Frame 1185)
  - Republic of South Africa, 1968/489
    - C-M (Reel 63, Frame 1)
  - Uganda, 1968/492
    - Makerere College (A-Z) (Reel 63, Frame 33)
    - A-W (Reel 63, Frame 177)
    - Uganda - Medical Sciences, 1968/492.A
      - Makerere College (Medical School) (Reel 63, Frame 230)
    - Uganda - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/492.D
      - Agriculture (K-N) (Reel 63, Frame 259)
    - Uganda - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/492.E
      - H-S (Reel 63, Frame 281)
    - Uganda - Social Sciences, 1968/492.S
      - Makerere College (P-S) (Reel 63, Frame 363)
  - Sudan, 1968/494
    - K-U (Reel 63, Frame 422)
  - West African Region, 1968/495
    - Administration (Reel 63, Frame 427)
    - O-R (Reel 63, Frame 591)
  - Ghana, 1968/496
    - B-U (Reel 63, Frame 803)
    - Ghana - Medical Sciences, 1968/496.A
      - University of Ghana (Medical School) (Reel 63, Frame 867)
    - Ghana - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/496.E
      - C-O (Reel 63, Frame 876)
  - Nigeria, 1968/497
    - Administration (Reel 63, Frame 902)
    - A-M (Reel 63, Frame 905)
    - University (I-L) (Reel 63, Frame 1033)
    - N-W (Reel 63, Frame 1144)
    - Nigeria - Medical Sciences, 1968/497.A
      - A-U (Reel 63, Frame 1179)
    - Nigeria - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/497.D
      - A-U (Reel 63, Frame 1217)
    - Nigeria - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/497.E
      - A-O (Reel 64, Frame 1)
    - Nigeria - Social Sciences, 1968/497.S
      - University of Ibadan (E-S) (Reel 64, Frame 46)
  - Sierra Leone, 1968/499
    - Sierra Leone (Education) (Reel 64, Frame 74)
    - N-W (Reel 64, Frame 196)
    - Sierra Leone - Natural Sciences, 1968/499.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 64, Frame 288)
  - France, 1968/500
    - E-W (Reel 64, Frame 312)
  - French Guiana, 1968/507
    - F-P (Reel 64, Frame 476)
  - Vietnam, 1968/509
    - T-V (Reel 64, Frame 514)
  - Cambodia, 1968/513
    - Pasteur Institute (Audebaud, G.) (Reel 64, Frame 517)
  - Ivory Coast, 1968/527
    - Bosso, N'Guetta (Reel 64, Frame 522)
    - Ivory Coast - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/527.D
      - Agriculture (H-S) (Reel 64, Frame 540)
    - Ivory Coast - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/527.E
      - Sakonoko (Reel 64, Frame 549)
  - Senegal, 1968/531
    - P-S (Reel 64, Frame 566)
  - Tunisia, 1968/539
    - A-T (Reel 64, Frame 578)
  - Asia, 1968/600
    - Administration (Reel 64, Frame 581)
    - Fisheries (Reel 64, Frame 599)
  - China, 1968/601
    - Chang, Hung-Chun (Reel 64, Frame 645)
  - Taiwan, 1968/605
    - Asian Vegetable Development Center (Reel 64, Frame 648)
    - A-Y (Reel 64, Frame 784)
  - Japan, 1968/609
    - A-Y (Reel 64, Frame 795)
    - Japan - Medical Sciences, 1968/609.A
      - N-O (Reel 64, Frame 983)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/609.E
      - Todani, Akio (Reel 64, Frame 992)
  - Korea, 1968/613
    - A-Y (Reel 64, Frame 995)
  - Thailand, 1968/617
    - Administration (January-June) (Reel 65, Frame 1)
    - Administration (July-December) (Reel 65, Frame 214)
    - Kasetsart University (A-S) (Reel 65, Frame 433)
    - A-P (Reel 65, Frame 578)
    - R-W (Reel 65, Frame 839)
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, 1968/617.A
      - R-U (Reel 65, Frame 1006)
    - Thailand - Nursing, 1968/617.C
      - R-S (Reel 65, Frame 1046)
    - Thailand - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/617.D
      - Agriculture (C-S) (Reel 65, Frame 1069)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/617.E
      - Thailand (Reel 65, Frame 1074)
      - A-P (Reel 66, Frame 1)
      - R-W (Reel 66, Frame 281)
    - Thailand - Social Sciences, 1968/617.S
      - Chulalongkorn University (Political Science) (Reel 66, Frame 448)
      - University of Thammasat (Economics) (Reel 66, Frame 451)
  - Holland, 1968/650
    - B-W (Reel 66, Frame 599)
  - Indonesia, 1968/652
    - B-S (Reel 66, Frame 718)
  - Europe, 1968/700
    - European Institute for Trans-National Studies (Reel 66, Frame 747)
  - Ethiopia, 1968/701
    - H-L (Reel 66, Frame 774)
    - Ethiopia - Medical Sciences, 1968/701.A
      - Haile Selassie I University (Medical School) (Reel 66, Frame 872)
  - Afghanistan, 1968/703
    - Shah, Aurang (Reel 66, Frame 881)
  - Austria, 1968/705
    - J-V (Reel 66, Frame 883)
  - Belgium, 1968/707
    - D-W (Reel 66, Frame 949)
  - Zaire, 1968/709
    Zaire
    - C-N (Reel 66, Frame 990)
    - Zaire - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/709.E
      - L-M (Reel 66, Frame 1177)
  - Yugoslavia, 1968/710
    - D-U (Reel 67, Frame 1)
  - Bulgaria, 1968/711
    - T-V (Reel 67, Frame 43)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1968/712
    - P-T (Reel 67, Frame 51)
  - Denmark, 1968/713
    - B-U (Reel 67, Frame 80)
    - Denmark -Nursing, 1968/713.C
      - Denmark - Nursing (Reel 67, Frame 155)
  - Iceland, 1968/715
    - Health (Sigurdsson, Sigurdur) (Reel 67, Frame 158)
  - Germany, 1968/717
    - B-W (Reel 67, Frame 160)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/717.E
      - Kreysler, Joachim V. (Reel 67, Frame 357)
  - Tanzania, 1968/723
    - K-U (Reel 67, Frame 369)
    - Tanzania - Medical Sciences, 1968/723.A
      - Dar es Salaam, School of Medicine (Monekosso, G. L.) (Reel 67, Frame 439)
    - Tanzania - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/723.D
      - Agriculture (Bryceson, Derek N. M.) (Reel 67, Frame 441)
    - Tanzania - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/723.E
      - C-S (Reel 67, Frame 456)
  - Zambia, 1968/724
    - University of Zambia (Anglin, Douglas G.) (Reel 67, Frame 495)
    - Zambia - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/724.E
      - Liswaniso, Malikana (Reel 67, Frame 527)
  - Cameroon, 1968/735
    - Cameroon - Medical Sciences, 1968/735.A
      - Medical School (Reel 67, Frame 529)
  - Greece, 1968/749
    - D-Z (Reel 67, Frame 637)
    - Greece - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/749.D
      - Agriculture (Hadjikos, Potis) (Reel 67, Frame 681)
  - Hungary, 1968/750
    - Balo, Joseph (Reel 67, Frame 689)
  - Italy, 1968/751
    - B-U (Reel 67, Frame 691)
  - Libya, 1968/758
    - University of Libya (A-D) (Reel 67, Frame 747)
  - Liberia, 1968/759
    - C-G (Reel 67, Frame 783)
    - Liberia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/759.D
      - University of Liberia (Agriculture) (Reel 67, Frame 858)
  - Morocco, 1968/765
    - M-U (Reel 67, Frame 877)
  - Norway, 1968/767
    - C-T (Reel 67, Frame 951)
  - Iran, 1968/771
    - S-Z (Reel 67, Frame 971)
  - Portugal, 1968/773
    - C-N (Reel 67, Frame 1094)
  - Romania, 1968/783
    - C-N (Reel 67, Frame 1115)
  - Russia, 1968/785
    - F-M (Reel 67, Frame 1121)
  - Finland, 1968/787
    - C-W (Reel 68, Frame 1)
  - Poland, 1968/789
    - B-S (Reel 68, Frame 10)
  - Spain, 1968/795
    - B-G (Reel 68, Frame 58)
  - Sweden, 1968/800
    - A-T (Reel 68, Frame 70)
  - Switzerland, 1968/803
    - C-N (Reel 68, Frame 135)
  - Near East Region, 1968/804
    - Arid Lands Agricultural Production Program (Reel 68, Frame 272)
  - Turkey, 1968/805
    - A-R (Reel 68, Frame 286)
    - Turkey - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/805.D
      - Agriculture (Gunay, Ekrem) (Reel 68, Frame 335)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1968/805.E
      - Fellowships (Reel 68, Frame 384)
      - B-S (Reel 68, Frame 386)
  - Egypt, 1968/812
    - A-C (Reel 68, Frame 392)
  - Jordan, 1968/816
    - A-J (Reel 68, Frame 421)
  - Saudi Arabi and Oman, 1968/817
    - Saudi Arabia and Oman - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/817.D
      - A (Reel 68, Frame 428)
  - Israel, 1968/825
    - I-T (Reel 68, Frame 440)
    - Israel - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1968/825.D
      - Agriculture (Shlomi, A.) (Reel 68, Frame 481)
  - Lebanon, 1968/833
    - A-D (Reel 68, Frame 483)
    - Lebanon - Medical Sciences, 1968/833.A
      - American University of Beirut (Reel 68, Frame 581)
  - Members and Meetings, 1968/903
    - Bingham, Barry (Reel 68, Frame 595)
    - Brace, Lloyd D. (Reel 68, Frame 604)
    - Bunche, Ralph J. (Reel 68, Frame 608)
    - Dickey, John S. (Reel 68, Frame 620)
    - Dillon, C. Douglas (Reel 68, Frame 632)
    - Ebert, Robert H. (Reel 68, Frame 648)
    - Franks of Headington, Oliver Shewell, Baron (Reel 68, Frame 672)
    - Goheen, Robert F. (Reel 68, Frame 738)
    - Hardin, Clifford M. (Reel 68, Frame 755)
    - Hesburgh, Theodore M. (Reel 68, Frame 771)
    - Houghton, Arthur A., Jr. (Reel 68, Frame 794)
    - Kerr, Clark (Reel 68, Frame 804)
    - Kimberly, John R. (Reel 68, Frame 812)
    - Lleras Camargo, Alberto (Reel 68, Frame 815)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd (Reel 68, Frame 835)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 4th (Reel 68, Frame 863)
    - Roosa, Robert V. (Reel 68, Frame 868)
    - Seitz, Frederick (Reel 68, Frame 887)
    - Stanton, Frank (Reel 68, Frame 940)
    - Watson, Thomas J., Jr. (Reel 68, Frame 965)
    - Wood, W. Barry, Jr. (Reel 68, Frame 988)
    - Young, Whitney M., Jr. (Reel 68, Frame 1010)
  - Humanities, 1968/911
    - Creative Writing (A-N) (Reel 68, Frame 1023)
  - Agriculture, 1968/923
    - Staff Candidates (K-T) (Reel 68, Frame 1174)
- General Correspondence, 1969
  - International, 1969/100
    - Belknap, Chauncey (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Borlaug, Norman E. (Reel 1, Frame 8)
    - Consultant (Boyce, Alfred M.) (Reel 1, Frame 131)
    - Consultant (Johnson, Glenn L.) (Reel 1, Frame 173)
    - Consultant (Stakman, Elvin C.) (Reel 1, Frame 186)
    - Consultants (A-K) (Reel 1, Frame 211)
    - Consultants (P-W) (Reel 1, Frame 270)
    - Diplomatic Services (A-W) (Reel 1, Frame 281)
    - Field Staff (Miscellaneous Memorandums) (Reel 1, Frame 478)
    - Hospitals (Skiff, Milton E.) (Reel 1, Frame 483)
    - Hotels (St. Lucia Beach) (Reel 1, Frame 490)
    - International Bank (B-S) (Reel 1, Frame 493)
    - International (A-E) (Reel 1, Frame 737)
    - International (F-V) (Reel 1, Frame 863)
    - Irwin, John N. (Reel 1, Frame 1009)
    - Myers, Will M. (Reel 1, Frame 1029)
    - Nickel, John L. (Reel 1, Frame 1055)
    - Quick, James S. (Reel 1, Frame 1130)
    - Rachie, Kenneth O. (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - Staff Members Occasional Papers (A-J) (Reel 2, Frame 197)
    - Staff Members Occasional Papers (L-O) (Reel 2, Frame 402)
    - Staff Members Occasional Papers (Parker, Dorothy) (Reel 2, Frame 604)
    - Staff Members Occasional Papers ( R) (Reel 2, Frame 733)
    - Staff Members Occasional Papers (S-Y) (Reel 2, Frame 892)
    - Streeter, Carroll P. (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - United Nations, Food and Agriculture Organization (A-Y) (Reel 3, Frame 117)
    - United Nations, Population Newsletter (Supplementary Material) (Reel 3, Frame 454)
    - United Nations (C-G) (Reel 3, Frame 457)
    - United Nations (H-J) (Reel 3, Frame 478)
    - United Nations (L-W) (Reel 3, Frame 730)
    - United Nations Development Programme (Goldschmidt, Arthur) (Reel 3, Frame 867)
    - United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization (A-S) (Reel 3, Frame 879)
    - United Nations Industrial Development Organization (Rothblum, E. G.) (Reel 3, Frame 924)
    - United Nations Research Institute for Social Development (Soler) (Reel 3, Frame 993)
    - Ai-An (Reel 3, Frame 996)
    - Ar-At (Reel 4, Frame 1)
    - Ba-Be (Reel 4, Frame 136)
    - Bl-Bo (Reel 4, Frame 324)
    - Br-By (Reel 4, Frame 384)
    - Ca-Ch (Reel 4, Frame 575)
    - Co-Cu (Reel 4, Frame 844)
    - D (Reel 4, Frame 954)
    - E (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - F (Reel 5, Frame 17)
    - G (Reel 5, Frame 60)
    - H (Reel 5, Frame 233)
    - I (Reel 5, Frame 470)
    - Ja-Je (Reel 5, Frame 526)
    - Jo-Ju (Reel 5, Frame 660)
    - K (Reel 5, Frame 827)
    - L (Reel 5, Frame 921)
    - Ma (Reel 5, Frame 1123)
    - Mc-Mi (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - Mo-My (Reel 6, Frame 140)
    - N (Reel 6, Frame 326)
    - O (Reel 6, Frame 429)
    - P (Reel 6, Frame 528)
    - Ra-Ri (Reel 6, Frame 721)
    - Ro (Reel 6, Frame 783)
    - Ru (Reel 6, Frame 958)
    - Sa-Sm (Reel 6, Frame 983)
    - So-Sp (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - St-Sy (Reel 7, Frame 186)
    - T-U (Reel 7, Frame 319)
    - Wa-Wi (Reel 7, Frame 486)
    - Wo (Reel 7, Frame 647)
    - Wr (Reel 7, Frame 938)
    - Y (Reel 7, Frame 1029)
    - International - Medical Sciences, 1969/100.A
      - World Council of Churches (Christian Medical Commission) (Reel 7, Frame 1060)
    - International - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1969/100.D
      - C-M (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - International - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1969/100.E
      - International (Reel 8, Frame 56)
      - Rankin, A. M. (Reel 8, Frame 61)
    - International - Virus Studies, 1969/100.V
      - United Nations, World Health Organization (Cockburn, W. Charles) (Reel 8, Frame 63)
  - Applications for Employment, 1969/101
    - D-K (Reel 8, Frame 69)
  - International Organizations, 1969/103
    - I-W (Reel 8, Frame 77)
  - United States, 1969/200
    - A-Af (Reel 8, Frame 175)
    - Agricultural Development Council (Wharton, Clifton R., Jr.) (Reel 8, Frame 374)
    - Agricultural Development Council (M-W) (Reel 8, Frame 595)
    - Ag (Reel 8, Frame 710)
    - Ai-Al (Reel 8, Frame 929)
    - Amafro Film Foundation (Reel 8, Frame 1073)
    - American (A) (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - American Council on Education (Africa Committee) (Reel 9, Frame 92)
    - American Council on Education (A-D) (Reel 9, Frame 208)
    - American (Ch-Co) (Reel 9, Frame 240)
    - American Cyanamid Company (White-Stevens, Robert H.) (Reel 9, Frame 487)
    - American (D-G) (Reel 9, Frame 562)
    - American (H-J) (Reel 9, Frame 751)
    - American (L-M) (Reel 9, Frame 885)
    - American Universities Field Staff, Inc. (H-M) (Reel 9, Frame 1072)
    - American University (H-W) (Reel 9, Frame 1082)
    - American (N-V) (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - Anacostia Community School Project (Supplementary Material) (Reel 10, Frame 223)
    - Am-Ap (Reel 10, Frame 493)
    - Aq-Ar (Reel 10, Frame 584)
    - Association (A-V) (Reel 10, Frame 644)
    - As (Reel 10, Frame 805)
    - At-Ay (Reel 10, Frame 956)
    - Ba (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - Be (Reel 11, Frame 140)
    - Bi-Bl (Reel 11, Frame 318)
    - Boston College (Human Science Institute) (Reel 11, Frame 418)
    - Bo (Reel 11, Frame 573)
    - Brookings Institution (L-O) (Reel 11, Frame 761)
    - Br (Reel 11, Frame 785)
    - Bu (Reel 11, Frame 961)
    - C-Cam (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - Can-Cav (Reel 12, Frame 170)
    - Center for the Arts of Indian America (Reel 12, Frame 484)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. (Reel 12, Frame 617)
    - Ce (Reel 12, Frame 685)
    - Ch (Reel 12, Frame 877)
    - Ci-Cl (Reel 12, Frame 1079)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. (E-T) (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - Columbia University (B-J) (Reel 13, Frame 140)
    - Columbia University (K-W) (Reel 13, Frame 263)
    - Coe-Col (Reel 13, Frame 467)
    - Composer in Performance, Inc. (Reel 13, Frame 616)
    - Com (Reel 13, Frame 706)
    - Consortium for Nigerian Rural Development (Herrmann, Omer W.) (Reel 13, Frame 899)
    - Con-Coo (Reel 13, Frame 933)
    - Cornell University (A-E) (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - Cornell University (F-M) (Reel 14, Frame 170)
    - Cornell University (N-W) (Reel 14, Frame 270)
    - Cor (Reel 14, Frame 477)
    - Cou-Coy (Reel 14, Frame 565)
    - Cr-Cu (Reel 14, Frame 736)
    - Dai-Dan (Reel 14, Frame 875)
    - Dar-Dav (Reel 14, Frame 1045)
    - De-Di (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Do-Du (Reel 15, Frame 151)
    - Education and World Affairs (A-P) (Reel 15, Frame 382)
    - Ea-Eg (Reel 15, Frame 414)
    - El-Em (Reel 15, Frame 607)
    - En-Ex (Reel 15, Frame 721)
    - Far West Laboratory for Educational Research and Development (Reel 15, Frame 811)
    - Fah-Fei (Reel 15, Frame 895)
    - Fel-Fin (Reel 15, Frame 1030)
    - Firehouse Theatre (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Fir-Fl (Reel 16, Frame 111)
    - Ford Foundation (A-G) (Reel 16, Frame 327)
    - Ford Foundation (H-J) (Reel 16, Frame 472)
    - Ford Foundation (L-W) (Reel 16, Frame 547)
    - Foundation Center (Reel 16, Frame 671)
    - Fo-Fr (Reel 16, Frame 769)
    - Fund for Education in World Order (Reel 16, Frame 945)
    - Fu (Reel 16, Frame 1062)
    - Ga-Gl (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - Go (Reel 17, Frame 238)
    - Gra (Reel 17, Frame 261)
    - Gre-Gu (Reel 17, Frame 393)
    - Harvard University (A-F) (Reel 17, Frame 529)
    - Harvard University (Science and Public Policy) (Reel 17, Frame 705)
    - Harvard University (G-Z) (Reel 17, Frame 715)
    - Haa-Har (Reel 17, Frame 961)
    - Hat-Haz (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - He-Hi (Reel 18, Frame 224)
    - Ho-Hy (Reel 18, Frame 352)
    - Indiana University (B-P) (Reel 18, Frame 531)
    - Institute for Educational Development (Reel 18, Frame 560)
    - Institute for Educational Development (Supplementary Material) (Reel 18, Frame 595)
    - Institute for the Future (Reel 18, Frame 795)
    - Institute (A-S) (Reel 18, Frame 889)
    - International (B-D) (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - International (M-T) (Reel 19, Frame 244)
    - Iowa State University (A-C) (Reel 19, Frame 440)
    - Iowa State University (F-W) (Reel 19, Frame 506)
    - I (Reel 19, Frame 651)
    - Ja-Je (Reel 19, Frame 953)
    - Johns Hopkins University (B-H) (Reel 19, Frame 970)
    - Johns Hopkins University (L-S) (Reel 20, Frame 1)